[
  [
    "The New Era of Accelerated Computing",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "NVIDIA Blackwell",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale AI Innovation Cloud",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the HGX B200",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the HGX B200",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Switch",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "15X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "second",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Transformer Engine",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Real-Time Inference",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "15X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "MoE",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "second",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Transformer Engine",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Blackwell Tensor Core",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NeMo",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "MoE",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "TTL",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "50ms",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "first",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "5s",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "32,768",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1,028",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "8x",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "eight",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1x",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "eight",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Next-Level Training Performance",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "second",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Transformer Engine",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "FP8",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "3X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "fifth",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1.8TB",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Switch",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Quantum",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "32,768",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "eight",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "H100",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "8",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "400",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "OpenAI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "the Latest AI Accelerators The Cirrascale AI Innovation Cloud",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Quantum",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specialized Cloud",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm’s AI Inference Suite The Qualcomm AI Inference Suite",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "San Diego",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Calif.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "March 6, 2025",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services ®",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Nick Pandher",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Technologies, Inc.",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Playground",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Cloud AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "LLM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "API",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942-3800",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services LLC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Technologies, Inc.",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Incorporated",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Mike",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Ready To Get Started",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "years",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "NLP / Audio Processing",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "daily",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "AWS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GCP",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Audio Processing",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Audio Processing News Tap",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the NVIDIA Developer News Center",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "over 500",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NLP",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Cirrascale Blog News",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Scale News 3.6.2025",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "3.6.2025",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "QUALCOMM",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "AGREE",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "TERMS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "TERMS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "TERMS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "CONDITIONS SET FORTH HEREIN",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1.",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "QUALCOMM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1.1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "License to Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Agreement",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1.2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "License to Documentation",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Agreement",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2.1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "QUALCOMM Incorporated or",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Snaptrack, Inc.",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "QUALCOMM Incorporated or",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Snaptrack, Inc.",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "third",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "third",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Lesser General Public License",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "LGPL",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "Mozilla",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "GPL",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "LGPL",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Mozilla",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "2.3 Third Party Code",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "third",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "third",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2.4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "2.5",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "third",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Section 1",
    "LAW"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "third",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "3",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "CONFIDENTIALITY",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "third",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "4.",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "5",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AGREE",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "EXPRESS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "QUALCOMM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "6",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "QUALCOMM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "QUALCOMM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "EXPRESS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NONINFRINGEMENT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "ACCURACY",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "RELIABILITY",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "6",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "LIABILITY",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "WITHOUT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "LIMITATION NEGLIGENCE",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "DIRECTORS",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "BUSINESS PROFITS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "DOWNLOAD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "INSTALLATION",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "SOFTWARE",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "LIABILITY",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NEGLIGENCE",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "ONE HUNDRED U.S. DOLLARS",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "INDEMNITY",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "third",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "8",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Agreement",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "9 and Section 11",
    "TIME"
  ],
  [
    "8",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "the United States",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "U.S.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "U.S.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "U.S.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "U.S.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "U.S.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Crimea – Region of",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Ukraine",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cuba",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Iran",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "North Korea",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Syria",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "U.S.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "U.S.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "EAR",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "15",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "C.F.R. §§ 730",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Department of Commerce, Bureau of Industry and Security",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Foreign Asset Control Regulations",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Department of Treasury",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Office of Foreign Assets Control",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "30",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "C.F.R.",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "500",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "9",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "the United States Government",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "DFARS 227 7202",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "10",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Agreement",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "QUALCOMM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "11",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "the State of California",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "The United Nations Convention on Contracts",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "San Diego County",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "California",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AUTHORITY",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "CONDITIONS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services ×",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Job Description Data Center Technician Locations",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Austin",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "TX Chicago",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "IL Charlotte",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "NC Jacksonville",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Middletown",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "a Data Center Technician",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Operations",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Linux",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Linux",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Operations",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "3+ years",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Linux",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Linux",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "50",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$25.21 - $35.00",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "40",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Dental",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Vision",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Monday to Friday",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "SAN JOSE",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Calif.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "March 18, 2025",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Inference Platform",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the NVIDIA Blackwell",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "6000",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Nick Pandher",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale Inference Platform",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale Inference Platform",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Retrieval Augmented",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Martin Woodall",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "DroneData",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Dave Salvator",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "U.S.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "April",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "the summer",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Inference Platform",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GTC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "###",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "BOCA Marketing Agency",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Mike",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Ready To Get Started",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Cerebras Systems",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "8x",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Faster Time",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Half",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Faster Time",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Unprecedented Flexibility",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Sunnyvale",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "CA",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "November 29, 2022",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras Systems",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NLP",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "the Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cerebras Cloud @ Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Transformer",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT-3",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras Wafer-Scale Clusters",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Andromeda AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "The Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "CS-2s",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "zero",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "multi-billion",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "months",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "multi-million dollar",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "The Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "half",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1.3 billion",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "175billion",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "8x",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "A100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "multi-billion",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "NLP",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "CS-2",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Andrew Feldman",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras Systems",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras",
    "FAC"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "The Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "The Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cerebras Wafer-Scale Cluster",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "first",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "16",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "up to 50,000",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "CS-2",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "less than one day",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "PJ Go",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1 to 20 billion",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "hundreds or thousands",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras Cloud",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "The Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "2-day",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "the Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "https://cirrascale.com/cerebras",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942-3800",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras Systems Cerebras Systems",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services LLC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Mike",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Ready To Get Started",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite ×",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite Inference Cloud",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite Efficient and",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "API",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Top Performance",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Future-Proofed Maximize",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Cloud AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "DevOps",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Inference Cloud Powered",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "the Qualcomm AI Inference Suite",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Mike LaPan",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "2025",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "CES",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Future Hinges on More",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "early January",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "NVIDIA",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GeForce",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "50",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "The True Essentials Behind AI Progress",
    "LAW"
  ],
  [
    "Today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "daily",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI Managed Services Drive Success",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale is",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Generative AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "three",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "The Cirrascale Inference Platform: Smarter Inferencing for Enterprise",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Scale News 3.6.2025",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "3.6.2025",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Cloud Storage Solutions",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Computer Vision",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NLP Workflows",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cloud Storage Benefits Local",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Autonomous Vehicle",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Natural Language Processing",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NLP",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Hot-Tier Storage Solutions Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "millions",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Quantum",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "S3",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Get Started",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "OpenAI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "the Latest AI Accelerators The Cirrascale AI Innovation Cloud",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI Accelerator",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Specialized Cloud",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale AI Innovation Cloud",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Monthly 3-Month Term",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "12-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "24-Month Term",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "36-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Instinct MI250",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "8-GPU",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "A100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "8-GPU",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "V100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "8-GPU",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Cloud AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "SambaNova",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services ×",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "thousands",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "San Diego",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "CA",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "July 12, 2022",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services®",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NLP",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "first",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "NPN",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "thousands",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "the past several quarters",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Mike LaPan",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Quantum",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Kubernetes",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "first",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Elite Cloud Services Provider for Visualization",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "NPN",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Bob Pette",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Professional Visualization, NVIDIA",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "A6000",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "1,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "8-GPU",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942-3800",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services LLC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "InfiniBand",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NVIDIA Corporation",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Mike",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Ready To Get Started",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Training Training Training",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Natural Language Processing",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Generative AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Computer Vision",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI Accelerator Partners",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Generative AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras Cerebras",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI Supercomputer",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "OAM Processor",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs System",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "8X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$22,499 $20,249 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "17,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Instinct MI250",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "$4,679 $4,211 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,743",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "OAM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "4X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "48-Core",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2.3",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB 1TB Local Storage",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Network 25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$22,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4,679",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$20,249 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4,211",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Annual",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$17,999 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,743",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs System",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$34,999 $31,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "27,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$26,499 $23,849 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "21,199",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "H100",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "24,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "22,499",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "19,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "Specs",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "48-Core",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Network 25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$34,999 $26,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "24,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$31,499 $23,849 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "22,499",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Annual",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$27,999 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "21,199",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "19,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Cloud AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Bare-Metal Pricing Config vCPUs System RAM Local Storage Monthly Pricing Annual",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "8X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128 512",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "$4,699 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,759",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Octo",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$2,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2,019",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$1,259 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "1,009",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$629 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "519",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GB 1TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "$549 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$369 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "289",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "12",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$329 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "259",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Config 8X AI 100 Ultra Octo AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "24 32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "32 12",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "RAM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "512",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GB",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "384",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "182",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$4,699 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "329",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "$3,759 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2,019",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "$439 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "289",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "259",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Technologies, Inc.",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "The Cerebras AI Model Studio Fine-Tuning - Standard Offering",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1K",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "2048",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "4096",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "6 $0.00055 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0023",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "17",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "132",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "20 $0.00190 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0039",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0078",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "56 451",
    "TIME"
  ],
  [
    "350",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "0.00003",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00006",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2.7 $0.00026 $0.0005 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0027",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6.1 $0.00065 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "16.1B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "16.1 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00147",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "44",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "350M CodeGen",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "2.7B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "CodeGen",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "16.1B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "6 20",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "16.1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1K",
    "QUANTITY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00055",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00190",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00003",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00026",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00065",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00147",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2048",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "0.0011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0039",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00006",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0005",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4096",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "0.0023",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0078",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0027",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "17",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AWS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "132",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "451",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "8",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "154 350",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "Chinchilla",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1-10%",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "~4-40B",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AWS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Model Training Model Parameters Tokens",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Train",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Train Cerebras AI Model Studio Price",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "26 0.4 $2,500",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "45,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6.7B 6.7",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "9 $60,000 GPT-3",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "13B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "260 39 $150,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "20",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "525,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "70",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "1,400",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "175B 175",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3,500",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Model GPT3-XL",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "11B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPT-3",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "175B",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "6",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "70 175",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Tokens",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Train",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "26",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "134 34",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "260",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1,400",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras AI Model Studio CS-2",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "9",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "39 47",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote Cerebras",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "525,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "Chinchilla",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Vertical Cooling Technology",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "late 2015",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Corporation",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "early 2017",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Corporation",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Guides",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Customer-Centric Cirracscale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Meet The Team",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Vertical Cooling Technology",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Mike LaPan",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Magna",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Amet Tempor",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Ipsum Adipiscing",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Dolore Sed",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Dolore Sit",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Red Hat",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Linux®",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Linux",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "millions",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Flash",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "IBM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI PowerAI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "IBM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Kubeflow",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "ML",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Kubernetes",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "ML",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Kubernetes",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Kubernetes",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Kubeflow",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "One",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "One",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Convergence",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "ML",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "CUDA",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Dkube",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "less than hour",
    "TIME"
  ],
  [
    "Tensorflow",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "PyTorch",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "ML",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "linear",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Press & Media Latest Stories",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "March 18, 2025",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "March 6, 2025",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services Announces Availability of Inference Cloud Powered",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm’s AI Inference Suite Learn",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "24/7/365",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HIPAA",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Physical Security Controls Access",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "two",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Digital Surveillance Extensive",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Power & HVAC Systems",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Facilities Monitoring",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942-3800",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Data Center Locations Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "U.S.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "US",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "US",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "US",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services ×",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Cerebras Cloud",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "8x",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "the Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale for Training and Fine Tuning",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "The Cerebras AI Model Studio The Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras CS-2’s",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "millions",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Transformer",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "weeks",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "tens of billions",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "up taking weeks",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "months",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Transformer",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "millions",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras CS-2",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "millions",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "over millions",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Zero DevOps",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "SSH",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Push",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "PyTorch",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "8x",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "up to 50,000",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "SSH",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "PyTorch",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "millions",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "a single minute",
    "TIME"
  ],
  [
    "half",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AWS Predictable",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Flexibility Train",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Ownership Dependency",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Simple & Secure Cloud Operations",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "DevOps",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Dataset",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Scratch Standard Offering",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1,000",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "10,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "White-Glove Support",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cerebras Wafer-Scale Cluster",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "SSH",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "Scripts",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Pile",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Save",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the hour CPU hours",
    "TIME"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale for dataset preparation",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "CPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "OAM Processor",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs System",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "8X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$22,499 $20,249 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "17,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Instinct MI250",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "$4,679 $4,211 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,743",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "OAM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "4X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "48-Core",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2.3",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB 1TB Local Storage",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Network 25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$22,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4,679",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$20,249 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4,211",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Annual",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$17,999 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,743",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs System",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$34,999 $31,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "27,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$26,499 $23,849 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "21,199",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "H100",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "24,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "22,499",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "19,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "Specs",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "48-Core",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Network 25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$34,999 $26,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "24,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$31,499 $23,849 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "22,499",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Annual",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$27,999 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "21,199",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "19,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Cloud AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Bare-Metal Pricing Config vCPUs System RAM Local Storage Monthly Pricing Annual",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "8X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128 512",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "$4,699 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,759",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Octo",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$2,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2,019",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$1,259 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "1,009",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$629 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "519",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GB 1TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "$549 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$369 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "289",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "12",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$329 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "259",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Config 8X AI 100 Ultra Octo AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "24 32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "32 12",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "RAM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "512",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GB",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "384",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "182",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$4,699 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "329",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "$3,759 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2,019",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "$439 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "289",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "259",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Technologies, Inc.",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "The Cerebras AI Model Studio Fine-Tuning - Standard Offering",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1K",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "2048",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "4096",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "6 $0.00055 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0023",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "17",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "132",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "20 $0.00190 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0039",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0078",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "56 451",
    "TIME"
  ],
  [
    "350",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "0.00003",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00006",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2.7 $0.00026 $0.0005 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0027",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6.1 $0.00065 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "16.1B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "16.1 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00147",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "44",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "350M CodeGen",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "2.7B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "CodeGen",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "16.1B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "6 20",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "16.1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1K",
    "QUANTITY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00055",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00190",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00003",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00026",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00065",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00147",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2048",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "0.0011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0039",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00006",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0005",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4096",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "0.0023",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0078",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0027",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "17",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AWS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "132",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "451",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "8",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "154 350",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "Chinchilla",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1-10%",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "~4-40B",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AWS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Model Training Model Parameters Tokens",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Train",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Train Cerebras AI Model Studio Price",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "26 0.4 $2,500",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "45,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6.7B 6.7",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "9 $60,000 GPT-3",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "13B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "260 39 $150,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "20",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "525,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "70",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "1,400",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "175B 175",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3,500",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Model GPT3-XL",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "11B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPT-3",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "175B",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "6",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "70 175",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Tokens",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Train",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "26",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "134 34",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "260",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1,400",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras AI Model Studio CS-2",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "9",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "39 47",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote Cerebras",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "525,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "Chinchilla",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Performance Computing",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale’s",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale’s",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale’s AI Innovation Cloud",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Advancing HPC",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the NVIDIA Developer News Center",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "over 500",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Multi-",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Largest Variety",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "two",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "the Latest Technology",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the years",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Offerings Dive",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Computer Vision Computer Vision Image",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AWS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GCP",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale’s AI Innovation Cloud",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Computer Vision Acceleration Partners The Latest Image Processing News Tap",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the NVIDIA Developer News Center",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "over 500",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Austin",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "The Network Operations Center",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NOC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NOC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NOC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "RMA",
    "EVENT"
  ],
  [
    "NOC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NOC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Austin",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Team Management: Lead",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NOC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Incident Management: Implement",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NOC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Generate",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Create NOC metrics",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cloud Engineering",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Customer Support",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "third",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Training & Development: Conduct",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NOC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Information Technology",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NOC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "5 years",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "at least 2 years",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Google Cloud",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Bash",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cisco CCNP",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AWS Certified SysOps Administrator",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Network+",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Soft Skills",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "regular business hours",
    "TIME"
  ],
  [
    "65,718.00",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "85,524.00",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "40",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Comprehensive",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Monday to Friday",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "8-hour",
    "TIME"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "the NVIDIA Inception Program",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "MosaicML",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Full Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "up to 30%",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "NVIDIA",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NPN CSP Elite Compute",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "RMA",
    "EVENT"
  ],
  [
    "Zero",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Referral Discounts Inception",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "up to 10%",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Inception",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Co-Marketing Opportunities",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Clusters Powered by NVIDIA HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Large-Scale AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "San Diego",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "CA",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "March 21, 2023",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services®",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "NVIDIA® HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "H100",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Hopper",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Mike LaPan",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "30X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "eight",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "NVLink",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NVSwitch",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Tensor Cores",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "H100",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "eight",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "InfiniBand",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Dave Salvator",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "H100",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942-3800",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942-3800",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services LLC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NVIDIA",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NVLink",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NVIDIA Corporation",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Mike",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Ready To Get Started",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Generative AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Generative AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Large Language Models",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cost-Effective Scalability",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Trust Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale’s AI Innovation Cloud",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Generative AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline Empowering AI Innovation",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Leading Accelerator Providers Core",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Accelerate Your Development",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Professional",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "zero",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Get Started What We Offer Solutions Designed for Seamless, Secure",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "Efficient AI Workflows Increase Performance Maximize",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "today",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "The Cirrascale AI Innovation Cloud",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU Cloud NVIDIA",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "GPU Cloud Unmatched End-to-",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Expand Horizons",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "HPC AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NVSwitch",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NVLink",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "more than 14x",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Gen4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "NDR",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Flexibility",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Inference ‍ Supports",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Provides",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Hugging Face",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Extensive Software Support",
    "FAC"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Simple & Secure Cloud Operations ‍",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "DevOps",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Popular NVIDIA Offerings",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale AI Innovation Cloud NVIDIA HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "The New Era of Accelerated Computing",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "second",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Transformer Engine",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "the HGX B200",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Switch",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "15X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "The World’s Leading AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "NVSwitch",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "an eight H200",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "eight",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "NVIDIA NVSwitch",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Tensor Cores",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "eight",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "HGX",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1.1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "HBM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "LLM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "175 billion",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "H100",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "NVSwitch",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "InfiniBand",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "up to 30%",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "OAM Processor",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs System",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "8X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$22,499 $20,249 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "17,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Instinct MI250",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "$4,679 $4,211 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,743",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "OAM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "4X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "48-Core",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2.3",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB 1TB Local Storage",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Network 25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$22,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4,679",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$20,249 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4,211",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Annual",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$17,999 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,743",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs System",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$34,999 $31,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "27,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$26,499 $23,849 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "21,199",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "H100",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "24,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "22,499",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "19,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "Specs",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "48-Core",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Network 25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$34,999 $26,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "24,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$31,499 $23,849 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "22,499",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Annual",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$27,999 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "21,199",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "19,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Cloud AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Bare-Metal Pricing Config vCPUs System RAM Local Storage Monthly Pricing Annual",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "8X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128 512",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "$4,699 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,759",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Octo",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$2,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2,019",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$1,259 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "1,009",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$629 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "519",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GB 1TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "$549 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$369 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "289",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "12",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$329 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "259",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Config 8X AI 100 Ultra Octo AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "24 32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "32 12",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "RAM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "512",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GB",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "384",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "182",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$4,699 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "329",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "$3,759 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2,019",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "$439 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "289",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "259",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Technologies, Inc.",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "The Cerebras AI Model Studio Fine-Tuning - Standard Offering",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1K",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "2048",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "4096",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "6 $0.00055 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0023",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "17",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "132",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "20 $0.00190 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0039",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0078",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "56 451",
    "TIME"
  ],
  [
    "350",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "0.00003",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00006",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2.7 $0.00026 $0.0005 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0027",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6.1 $0.00065 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "16.1B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "16.1 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00147",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "44",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "350M CodeGen",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "2.7B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "CodeGen",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "16.1B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "6 20",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "16.1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1K",
    "QUANTITY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00055",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00190",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00003",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00026",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00065",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00147",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2048",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "0.0011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0039",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00006",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0005",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4096",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "0.0023",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0078",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0027",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "17",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AWS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "132",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "451",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "8",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "154 350",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "Chinchilla",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1-10%",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "~4-40B",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AWS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Model Training Model Parameters Tokens",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Train",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Train Cerebras AI Model Studio Price",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "26 0.4 $2,500",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "45,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6.7B 6.7",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "9 $60,000 GPT-3",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "13B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "260 39 $150,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "20",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "525,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "70",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "1,400",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "175B 175",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3,500",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Model GPT3-XL",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "11B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPT-3",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "175B",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "6",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "70 175",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Tokens",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Train",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "26",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "134 34",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "260",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1,400",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras AI Model Studio CS-2",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "9",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "39 47",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote Cerebras",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "525,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "Chinchilla",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Monday - Friday",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "8am to 5pm Pacific Time",
    "TIME"
  ],
  [
    "888",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "942-3800",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Detail",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services ×",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "AI Accelerator Partners",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "OAM Processor",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs System",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "8X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$22,499 $20,249 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "17,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Instinct MI250",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "$4,679 $4,211 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,743",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "OAM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "4X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "48-Core",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2.3",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB 1TB Local Storage",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Network 25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$22,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4,679",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$20,249 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4,211",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Annual",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$17,999 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,743",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs System",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$34,999 $31,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "27,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$26,499 $23,849 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "21,199",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "H100",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "24,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "22,499",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "19,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "Specs",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "48-Core",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Network 25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$34,999 $26,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "24,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$31,499 $23,849 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "22,499",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Annual",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$27,999 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "21,199",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "19,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Cloud AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Bare-Metal Pricing Config vCPUs System RAM Local Storage Monthly Pricing Annual",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "8X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128 512",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "$4,699 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,759",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Octo",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$2,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2,019",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$1,259 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "1,009",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$629 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "519",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GB 1TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "$549 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$369 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "289",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "12",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$329 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "259",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Config 8X AI 100 Ultra Octo AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "24 32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "32 12",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "RAM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "512",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GB",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "384",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "182",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$4,699 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "329",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "$3,759 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2,019",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "$439 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "289",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "259",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Technologies, Inc.",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "The Cerebras AI Model Studio Fine-Tuning - Standard Offering",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1K",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "2048",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "4096",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "6 $0.00055 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0023",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "17",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "132",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "20 $0.00190 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0039",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0078",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "56 451",
    "TIME"
  ],
  [
    "350",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "0.00003",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00006",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2.7 $0.00026 $0.0005 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0027",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6.1 $0.00065 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "16.1B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "16.1 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00147",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "44",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "350M CodeGen",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "2.7B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "CodeGen",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "16.1B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "6 20",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "16.1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1K",
    "QUANTITY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00055",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00190",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00003",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00026",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00065",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00147",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2048",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "0.0011",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0039",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00006",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0005",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4096",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "0.0023",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0078",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.00013",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0027",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "0.0030",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "17",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AWS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "132",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "451",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "8",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "154 350",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "Chinchilla",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1-10%",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "~4-40B",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "10B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras AI Model Studio",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AWS",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Model Training Model Parameters Tokens",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Train",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Train Cerebras AI Model Studio Price",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "26 0.4 $2,500",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "45,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6.7B 6.7",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "9 $60,000 GPT-3",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "13B",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "260 39 $150,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "20",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "525,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "70",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "1,400",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "175B 175",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3,500",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Model GPT3-XL",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "11B",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPT-3",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPT",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "175B",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "6",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "70 175",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Tokens",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Train",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "26",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "134 34",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "260",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1,400",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Cerebras AI Model Studio CS-2",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "9",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "39 47",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Contact For Quote Contact For Quote Cerebras",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "525,000",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "T5",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "Chinchilla",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "Decline",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "the Cirrascale AI Innovation Cloud",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Matrix Core Technologies",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Software",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Generative AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD Infinity Fabric Technology Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "eight",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "800",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AMD EPYC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Instinct",
    "NORP"
  ],
  [
    "Infinity Fabric",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "CPU",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirracale Optimal Performance",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Generative AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Hugging Face",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Simple & Secure Cloud Operations Simple",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "DevOps",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD Products",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "3",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Matrix Core Technologies",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "AI",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Instinct MI250",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Instinct MI250",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "first",
    "ORDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "U.S.",
    "GPE"
  ],
  [
    "Instinct MI250",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "Matrix Core Technologies",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "HPC",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "OAM Processor",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs System",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "8X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$22,499 $20,249 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "17,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Instinct MI250",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "$4,679 $4,211 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,743",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "OAM",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "4X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "AMD",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "48-Core",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2.3",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB 1TB Local Storage",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Network 25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$22,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4,679",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$20,249 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "4,211",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Annual",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$17,999 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,743",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Specs System",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$34,999 $31,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "27,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "H200",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$26,499 $23,849 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "21,199",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "H100",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "24,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "22,499",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "19,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale Cloud Services",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "one",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GPU",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "B200",
    "PRODUCT"
  ],
  [
    "Specs",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "48-Core",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "960",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "4",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Network 25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "25Gb Bonded",
    "PERCENT"
  ],
  [
    "3200Gb Available",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Monthly",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$34,999 $26,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "24,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "6-Month",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$31,499 $23,849 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "22,499",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Annual",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "$27,999 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "21,199",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "19,999",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Cirrascale's No Surprises",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "Qualcomm Cloud AI",
    "PERSON"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "Bare-Metal Pricing Config vCPUs System RAM Local Storage Monthly Pricing Annual",
    "WORK_OF_ART"
  ],
  [
    "8X",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128 512",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "2",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "3.84",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "$4,699 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "3,759",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Octo",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$2,499 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "2,019",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$1,259 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "1,009",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$629 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "519",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "GB 1TB",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "$549 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "32",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$369 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "289",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "12",
    "DATE"
  ],
  [
    "48",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "1",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "$329 $",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "259",
    "MONEY"
  ],
  [
    "Config 8X AI 100 Ultra Octo AI",
    "ORG"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "128",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "64",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
    "100",
    "CARDINAL"
  ],
  [
